<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Atlanta House of Hope</title>
        <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Atlanta House of Hope</description>

         
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Know Your Rights</title>
                    <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/know-your-rights/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:25:34 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Everyone in the United States has certain rights. Watch these videos to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>About Us</title>
                    <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/about-us/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>Atlanta House of Hope Mission Statement The Atlanta House of Hope, Inc., was founded by concerned community members seeking to protect children affected by immigration enforcement actions which impact their families. The immigration enforcement policies of the United States could potentially affect the living conditions for millions of immigrant families in 2025 – and many of the affected people will be children who are U.S. citizens. The House of Hope is here to protect these children.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Documents</title>
                    <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/documents/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Anyone can download and print these documents for no cost.  Beware of anyone that tries to charge you a fee to access documents.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>FAQs</title>
                    <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/faqs/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>What is AHH? The Atlanta House of Hope is a group of concerned citizens working to ensure that U.S. Citizen children do not become incarcerated, homeless, or wards of the state – in the event that their undocumented immigrant parents are arrested, detained, or deported.</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Other Resources</title>
                    <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/other-resources/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>Food pantries - https://www.acfb.org/get-help/food-map/&#xA;Georgia Latino Alliance For Human Rights - https://glahr.org/&#xA;Georgia Legal Aid: Immigration - https://www.georgialegalaid.org/issues/immigrant-rights-immigration&#xA;Nonprofit organizations in Georgia that advocate for immigrants - https://www.immigrationadvocates.org/nonprofit/legaldirectory/search?state=GA&#xA;ACLU - Know Your Rights | Immigrants’ Rights - https://www.aclu.org/know-your-rights/immigrants-rights&#xA;GALEO: Supporting Georgia’s Latino community - https://galeo.org&#xA;Latino Community Fund (LCF) - https://lcfgeorgia.org/</description>
                </item>
                
            
                 
                <item>
                    <title>Understanding Warrants</title>
                    <link>https://atlantahouseofhope.org/understanding-warrants/</link>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:21:18 -0500</pubDate>
                    <description>Use these resources to learn the difference between an ICE Warrant and a Valid Judicial Warrant&#xA;Valid Judicial Warrant: A valid judicial warrant is signed by a “U.S. Magistrate or Judge” under the signature line. The name, date, and address must all be correct. If they present a valid judicial warrant (signed by a judge or magistrate), then only the person who is named on the warrant should step out of the home and close the door behind them to keep others in the home safe.</description>
                </item>
                
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
